<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<hash>
  <1241604>
    <description>&amp;#149;Great location in Crestview Hills &amp;#150; near St. Elizabeth Hospital (off Thomas More Parkway) and convenient to I-275, I-75, Crestview Hills Town Center, grocery stores, restaurants, entertainment and much more. &amp;#149;Less than 15 minutes from: Airport, downtown Cincinnati, Covington, Florence, Hebron and other Northern KY communities</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </1241604>
  <984463>
    <description>Truely cozy wood-panelled cabin. Open floor plan with bedroom open to large family or living room. Kitchen and dining area are two steps down. Stack laundry connections located in bathroom. This home has been used by a variety of sculptors over the past several years and has a special ambience. The large metal studio behind the house is also for rent at %575. House comes with half use of boat dock. Full use of boat dock, house rent is $725Brokered And Advertised By: Dallas Buyer's AgentsListing Agent: Stephen Ritchey</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </984463>
  <809457>
    <description>Enjoy luxury living in an inviting, master-planned community that is modern and developed for play, work and enjoyment. Unwind in a stunning maintenance-free (do not even have to change your own light-bulb) apartment home with finishes of a custom home, including: lamenent hardwood entries &amp; kitchens, ceramic-tile bathrooms, maple-finished cabinetry, chef caliber kitchens with adjustable track lighting, full-size washer and dryer, berber carpeting, nine-foot and vaulted ceilings and enormous oversized closets. The blvd offers a choice of one and two bedroom apartments and two bedroom lofts. The blvd is a classic private sanctuary built with you specifically in mind. Visit this charismatic destination because the blvd is just the place you want to be!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </809457>
  <1146658>
    <description>Oasis is a brand new high rise luxury condominium, in Fort Myers Florida! Our resort style community, located in the River District of Fort Myers offers beautiful water views from our large 2 and 3 bedroom condominium homes. Each home offers floor to ceiling windows, stainless steel appliances, granite countertops, Italian cabinetry, porcelain flooring in kitchen and baths, separate glass enclosed shower and whirlpool tub. We have available high speed internet access, 24 hour controlled access, and a marina with direct access to the Gulf of Mexico. Oasis is located within walking distance to Centennial Park, shopping, dining and art galleries. You will also be a short drive to Fort Myers Beach, Sanibel and Captiva, I-75, Highway 41 and Fort Myers International Airport.</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </1146658>
  <1026868>
    <description>Welcome to the beautiful Morton Manor in Ridley Park. We have a wonderful one bedroom first floor apartment available. Tenants are responsible only for the apartment electricity. The landlord is responsible for gas heat, hot water, cold water, trash, common area electric and landscaping. These apartments consist of spacious kitchens and extremely large floor plans. Additionally, we offer personal storage areas in the basement as well as coin operated laundry facilities. Apt Management serves as the property manager with 24 hour emergency maintenance. We are here to serve all your needs! Please visit our website at www.ridleyparkapartments.com to see more details for this property and many others properties in Delaware County. Great credit and great income only require first month, move in fees and security deposit. Okay credit and okay income require first month, last month, move in fees and security deposit. Dogs (non-aggressive breeds) and cats are accepted with a $300 non-refundable pet fee upfront in addition to $25 per month pet fee charge.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>On-Site Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Cats Allowed</amenity>
      <amenity>Dogs Allowed</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1026868>
  <511246>
    <description>Incredible home close to interstate, but tucked away for pricacy on a large, cul-de-sac lot. Huge, covered front porch. 2 master suites. Oversized bedrooms. Open kitchen with island and new counters. Spacious master suite upstairs with private balcony and sitting area. Full finished basement boasts a den with gas fireplace, office, bedroom and full than. Bathrooms offer new cabinets and granite counters. Absolutely Immaculate. Also available for sale #4154184 Must see!!!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </511246>
  <1064308>
    <description>Need a place to call home. How about this 2 bedroom, 1 bath home. Includes all appliances,washer/dryer, a/c unit, 3 season room, nice large yard, parking. Owner will take care of lawn and most of the snow removal. You are responsible for all utilities, removing snow from steps to parking area, oil. No pets and no smoking. Available after June 1, 2011</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1064308>
  <1067772>
    <description>1 Bedroom apartments available in Collingswood. 1st and 2nd floor. LOCATION, LOCATION, LOCATION! Take advantage of the town&amp;#39;s many amenities. PATCO speedline station, farmer&amp;#39;s market, shopping, restaurants, parks. Living room, Bedroom, Kitchen and bathroom. Off street parking available for one car and INCLUDES HEAT! Call for an application today, good credit please.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Public Transit</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1067772>
  <1015231>
    <description>Better than new! Grand 2 story entry with detailed ceiling. Formal rooms with detailed mouldings. Wood floors, large den with gas log FP, tiled sunroom, large kitchen with granite tops. Large playroom on lower level with FP. Professionally landscaped lot with sprinkler system. Wall to beautiful neighbood pool!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1015231>
  <445001>
    <description>Sublet.com Listing ID 1716314. I live in a beautiful house on over an acre of land in Paisley Florida which backs up on the Ocala National Forest. I live on lakefront property where all kinds of activities can be had from skiing to incredible fishing. Tenant will have access to boat and motor. There is plenty of parking and room for storage. The house is tongue and groove cypress wood which is beautiful. I own a bird and dog and she is on an invisible fence system which any dog can be added to. It is very private and quiet with lots of property. There is also a kayak available to use. There are 1 and a half bathrooms. There is central heat and air. Very nice kitchen and laundry room. There is a carport and a huge 2 car garage and a shed. There is no crime in this neighborhood. The house is beautiful and was built in 1954. There is a workshop with tools available for use. There is a great dock with boat next to it. Hardly anyone uses the lake and it is springfed. There are a multitude of outdoor activities in this area and u are close to Deland and New SmyrnaDaytona Beach.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Dogs Allowed</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </445001>
  <720388>
    <description>Sophistication, Style and Class in the heart of Layton. Layton Meadows is situated in the perfect location within walking distance to exceptional dining, shopping and theaters and just seconds from Hill Air Force Base. As you step into the remodeled apartment homes you will notice no detail has been overlooked. Visit our top notch community today!</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </720388>
  <970750>
    <description>NICE 4 BEDROOM WITH 3 FULL BATHS HOME ON 4 WOODED ACRES IN SPLENDORA. THIS HOME HAS A HUGE LIVING ROOM AND A HUGE DEN. 2 MASTER BEDROOMS; 1 HAS A STUDY OR SITTING AREA, GARDEN TUB WITH BLOCK TILES FOR PLENTY OF LIGHT AND SEPARATE SHOWER. ISLAND KITCHEN WITH DISHWASHER AND STOVE. LARGE WOODEN DECK AND STORAGE SHED IN THE BACK.Brokered And Advertised By: EXIT REALTY NE HOUSTONListing Agent: Fred Atkins</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </970750>
  <290917>
    <description>home with fenced yard, playground, central air, washer and dryer, vaulted ceilings, granite countertops and many more upgrades. Slate and tile floors in kitchen and bath. Home also has an extra deep garage, planter boxes and 2" blinds. For more information, to schedule a showing or to see what else is available call 801-621-2121 or go to http://www.froerer.net This property is being offered by Froerer Real Estate Inc. Utah property management and real estate investing.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </290917>
  <391244>
    <description>Rental opportunity in a fantastic lake access community , this ground floor unit is just a short walk to the beach via it's own tunnel !!!! ample parking , trash removal and all exterior maintenance are just a few of the amenities this unit has to offer. Enjoy morning Coffee in the enclosed porch overlooking New found lake and Mount Cardigan. Large Kitchen is well appointed and open to the Dining room for conversation . The living room is wonderful for conversation , 2 large bedrooms with ample closet space, a utility room with washer and dryer. in the Spring and Summer enjoy Tennis on the private court , this property has much to offer for all 4 seasons.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </391244>
  <1159472>
    <description>Chesterfield Apartments welcomes you to a unique living experience. At Chesterfield, you can have it ALL! We offer several different floorplans to meet your needs. The community is nestled in Suburban Southwest Houston, and conveniently located to shopping, restaurants and freeway access. We offer serene, suburban surroundings amidst one of the fastest-growing areas in Houston, a quick commute to the Galleria or downtown and just minutes from Highway 6, Highway 59, and Beltway 8. You will also find fine shopping and dining close by. We strive to offer the highest quality living accommodations in a gracious community.</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </1159472>
  <977202>
    <description>Hidden Treasure! This charming home located on a non-through street is very private and sits among old oak trees with a view of green space. The house has been recently updated and includes a master suite, hardwood floors, 2 wood burning fireplaces, tankless water heater and central A/C to name but a few of the extras. Take in the view and tranquility while cooking in a recently installed outdoor kitchen nestled in stone. Includes washer/dryer, refigerator &amp; microwave. This is a perfect place to enjoy the Sierra Madre lifestyle. Note that the 4th bedroom does not have a closet. Property is also listed for sale at $879,000.Brokered And Advertised By: Podley PropertiesListing Agent: Laura Stone</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </977202>
  <371696>
    <description>Located in a triplex just outside of downtown San Anselmo is this clean 2 bedroom, 1 bathroom unit. Inside this bright unit features clean carpet, fireplace, dishwasher and more! Additionally there is a spacious front deck, shared 1 car garage and shared laundry facilities. Water is included in the rent. This is a no pets and non-smoking property. If you would like to make an appointment to view this property please contact Matt (415) 482-9977 ext. 213 or email him directly at matt@prandiprop.com. Thank you.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>On-Site Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </371696>
  <422018>
    <description>Lake view! Immavulate 2-story chalet on double lot with private lake access. Chimney chase and paint. Front and back decks. New roof, large shady, fenced backyard. Finished basement. 2 car garage w/extraspace for boat. New elementary school open August 2010.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </422018>
  <1392972>
    <description>Pont Alba Apartments in Bellaire, TX is a 92 unit apartment community managed by Harvest Management offering 5 different floor plans ranging from $885 to $1320 per month. This floor plan is subject to a $50 application fee, $125 refundable deposit and $125 nonrefundable deposit. Pet policies allow cats and dogs up to 120 pounds with a $200 nonrefundable pet fee. Breed Restrictions Apply.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Cats Allowed</amenity>
      <amenity>Dogs Allowed</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1392972>
  <324772>
    <description>This spacious home located just off of highway 133 in the private gated community of Cedar Creek comes with a boat slip. The home itself overlooks the community tennis court and is within walking distance of the lake. Great place for the family to swim, relax and enjoy lake living. The property is less than 15 minutes from Clemson University or Pickens SC. Lake Keowee is a 23 mile long, 18,500 acre lake that has been voted one of the cleanest lakes in the South East. Several golf courses in the general area. There are restaurants located on the water as well as within easy driving distance. Close to many waterfalls, scenic rivers, and surrounded by mountains; once you stay you will want to come back year after year!</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </324772>
  <559655>
    <description>Little River Inn is located just 5 minutes from the Cherry Grove beaches and only a short drive to Myrtle Beach. The community has 2 large pools, a jacuzzi, tennis courts and volleyball play area. There is a private community trash bin along with security features throughout the community. Little River Inn is located off Highway 17 south at the intersection of Highway 17south and Highway 9. Please call 1- 800 869-5770 for additional information</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </559655>
  <1089686>
    <description>Spacious 7 bedroom 4.5 bathroom house located on a friendly cul de sac. Just under 3,000 sq feet, but since this is such a great lay out, the house feels much bigger! One master/granny suite is downstairs with a full bathroom great for guest. Half down as well The main master is up stairs and is very large. Big enough for a private sitting area,work out area+!! Master bath offers a large walk in closest with organizers, separate shower and tub, his and her sinks! 6 other bedrooms and 2 full bathrooms are also up stairs. Heating and AC Ceiling fans throughout. Hard wood floors through out the house. Tile in kitchen, bathrooms and in side laundry room.Perfect house for those with allergies since there is NO CARPET!!! Spacious kitchen offer honey oak cabinets, large center island with 4 burner gas cook top. Microwave/oven combo and dishwasher. 2 sets of french doors to patios. Back yard has a small grass area. Only 20 minutes to down town. With in 10 miles to MCS Miramar Easy access to I-15 shopping ,dinning, gas stations,Costco. Scripps offers Community fair FREE Concerts in the park Fourth of July Parade Local rec center Great parks Miramar lake. Farmers market Swim and racket club Top Schools: Ellen Browing Scripps (EBS) k-5 Marshall middle school 6-8 Scripps Ranch high school 9-12 Innovations academy, Come drive by the house to see if the location is ideal for you. 12065 Cassini court 92131, the house is the 4th of the left toward to the end of the street. Or for more info please call 858-740-7406. Rent is $2995. a month with a $3,500 security deposit. Renter pays all water +utilities. Including showing/having proof of renters insurance. This is a non smoking house. $35.00 credit/application fee that will need to be paid in cash. this will not be returned.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Ceiling Fan</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1089686>
  <998934>
    <description>Fabulous free standing waterfront Goat Island townhouse w/parking and panoramic views, great deck facing Newport Harbor. Spacious 2 level floor plan w/cathedral ceilings, open LR, DR, kitchen area on 1st floor. Master BR &amp; bath on 2nd floor. Private setting, 24hr security, gated community, pool, tennis, marina, water shuttle to downtown Newport. Rental available year round or enjoy a summer get away! ~More affordable, more room and more amenities than any hotel!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Public Transit</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </998934>
  <670210>
    <description>Experience the finest in apartment living at Brentwood Downs . Conveniently located just minutes from I-85 in the heart of Gwinnett County, close to parks, shopping and a large selection of fine dining. Enjoy a stroll around the lake or just relax at the gazebo. You could also use the state of the art fitness center and then lay out by our beautiful pool and enjoy the wooded views. While falling asleep at night in one of our large 1, 2, or 3-bedroom homes, enjoy the sound of the fountain located at the center of the lake. Our apartment homes offer attractive features such as crown molding, chair rails, built in book shelves, energy saving appliances, fireplaces, washer/dryer connections and large screened in patios. Come see why Brentwood Downs is more than a place to call home.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Hookup</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </670210>
  <368837>
    <description>Large One Bedroom with Water, Sewer, Trash, Hot Water and Parking. Electric baseboard heat. Average electric bill is less than $40! Wood flooring in the living room and carpet in the bedroom. Pets OK. 24 hour notice for all showings. Brokered And Advertised By: DM Rothwell, Inc Listing Agent: Bet Rothwell</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Cats Allowed</amenity>
      <amenity>Dogs Allowed</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </368837>
  <1149756>
    <description>This listing is for the leasing of barns and pasteur area only! Owner will consider subdividing. Fantastic horse facility! Breed! Train, Board! 3 Barns, 55 stalls, brood mare barn, indoor track, indoor round pen-bull ring, numerous fenced pastures, paddock, pond, tack &amp; feed room, hayloft w/2500+ bales, storage, separate office, apartment in barn for help, wash rack, laundry, farrier station, lot acre hayfield.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>On-Site Laundry</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1149756>
  <81119>
    <description>Cass City offers 24 spacious one-bedroom apartments for seniors 62 or older. Come and join our tenants in the community room that is always buzzing with activity. If you prefer more solitude, each apartment has it's own patio with country scenic views. All of our apartments are on ground level, with 24 hour maintenance and an on site manager for all your rental needs. For further information please contact us at the above address and phone number.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </81119>
  <309251>
    <description>Beautiful Hollywood Hills 3 bedroom 1 3/4 bathroom home wth extra large backyard overlooking the world famous Hollywood Sign in the Lake Hollywood Estates area. Both the formal living room and the formal dining room have fireplaces. The large master has a walk-in closet. The kitchen has a stove, oven, broiler, dishwasher and an adjacent interior laundry room. There is all new paint and flooring. &amp;#xD;&amp;#xA; &amp;#xD;&amp;#xA;You'll appreciate the adjacent double car attached garage.&amp;#xD;&amp;#xA;&amp;#xD;&amp;#xA;This home is beautifully landscaped. The gardening serice is included in the rent. All utilities are the responsibility of the tenant. Must have good credit and references. No smokers or large pets. Submit information regarding small pets. (A separate deposit will be required.)&amp;#xD;&amp;#xA;The home has a home warranty policy on it. Brokered And Advertised By: Woodbridge Estates Inc. Listing Agent: Sharrell Treat</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </309251>
  <1380090>
    <description>Check out this great home in Holly Ridge! Minutes from the base or the beach it is spacious and offers several amenities such as a large back deck, tile shower, Tile countertops, washer and dryer and lawn service! It is priced right at $900 a month and we are willing to talk about pets. Hurry! This home usually doesn't last long!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1380090>
  <1064105>
    <description>Solid older home with gorgeous antique hardwood floors, pine tongue-and-groove planks cover all the interior walls. Age has turned all the wood to a deep honey golden-red. New kitchen floor, all hardwood floors just revarnished. Nice yard with a little creek running through it, and lots of garden space up behind the house in a 2-3 acre meadow. Seperate garage, and storage building for renter use. Big Buck Stove in main room heats everything with fuel oil, even when the power is out. Lots of windows and views, with screens and storm windows. Big walk in closet in main hall, closets in bedrooms are limited.3 Bedrooms, two have beautiful oak floors, the third has carpet. Big walk in closet at the end of the hall, between two bedrooms, and two bedrooms have closets. Big concrete storage shed behind house available for renter.Comes equipped with washer and dryer, and an electric range.No pets please because of the hardwood floors.$500 security deposit and first month rent before move-in, and $20 with application so we may run credit and background check. Ideal for the person with a green thumb or someone that wants room for large garden.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1064105>
  <522578>
    <description>Step up to Waterstone, a new collection of one- and two-bedroom apartment homes set amidst the growing community of Tracy, just 20 minutes east of the Bay Area. Step into luxury. At Waterstone, you'll enjoy a variety of floorplans and conveniences, including multiple broadband outlets, full-size washers and dryers plus a well equipped kitchen with maple cabinetry and energy-efficient appliances. Here you'll relish the best of amenities: tall ceilings with deep crown molding, ceiling fans and track lighting, built-in desks and roomy walk-in closets. Step away from the city and into comfortable small-town life. Waterstone's location, just moments from freeway access, puts you within easy reach of a multitude of Northern California destinations from bustling San Francisco and Sacramento to the serenity of Lake Tahoe. Nearby, parks, abundant shopping and conveniences help keep life simple. And Tracy's welcoming village atmosphere makes weekends a true retreat. Step towards your future at Waterstone. Join Moonlight Madness at Waterstone on 2/13 from 11am to 10pm. Receive late night specials including reduced rents, $13 deposits and application fees for one day only! Ask for details.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Ceiling Fan</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </522578>
  <940460>
    <description>Sibley Estates Senior Apartments in Henderson Minnesota offers everything you need and deserve at an affordable price. Our one bedroom apartments are designed for seniors 62 years of age or better, or people with disabilities. Our apartments feature controlled access to the building, an elevator for convenience, a social room for entertainment, a large laundry room, and a friendly caring staff. Come and tour today!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>On-Site Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Disabled Access</amenity>
      <amenity>Elevator</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </940460>
  <887959>
    <description>Heritage Square offers you a lifestyle of comfort and elegance. Far enough away from it all yet conveniently close enough to work, schools (Midway ISD) and a variety of shopping amenities, our apartments are everything you've been looking for. Our well-priced contemporary units are generously appointed and feature large walk-in closets, washer/dryer connections (an on-site clothes-care center is also available), dishwashers and garbage disposals. To add to your comfort, your new place also comes complete with an oversized patio or balcony. Our beautifully landscaped grounds are meticulously manicured by our devoted maintenance team and make for serene and relaxing surroundings. Our professional team is eager to attend to any concern or service call in a most timely and courteous manner. Last but not least, don't forget to take advantage of our recreation-rich setting. Our sparkling pool and sundeck are perfect to unwind after a long day while our tennis court is what you need to reenergize!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>Garbage Disposal</amenity>
      <amenity>In-Unit Hookup</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </887959>
  <419635>
    <description>Luxury living at an affordable price...Silver Creek Apartments are located close to shopping and restaurants. The apartment homes include brand new appliances including microwave and dishwasher, central heat and air. Our community features an indoor fitness center, media room, cyber cafe, sports court and a tot play area. Friendly on-site maintenance staff. Pets welcome.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </419635>
  <567597>
    <description>Great Floor plan, new Spacious 3320 sq ft 5bdrm, (4 Bedroom / 1 office) 3 full Baths; bonus room &amp; courtyard. All brand new carpet / custom paint, travertine / porcelain floors. Home on 8k sqft Large Corner lot, with great back yard for kids and entertaining. Right next to Red Rock, hiking, atv riding from the front door: Very quite and safe community, with parks and streets kids can play in. Private Sub Gate "Granada Palomar". All Bedrooms are spacious with walk in or large closets. Master Bedroom Suite has Double (separate vanity sinks) with a separate make-up vanity, and a custom Tub, Large walk in closet. Great Kitchen with miles of storage and granite counter space &amp; island &amp; table area. Dinning room features Butler&amp;rsquo;s Pantry, with even more storage. Home also features, Over sized wash room, walk in pantry and Walk in Linen closet. Bonus room has built in computer desk, with a large outdoor Patios featuring Incredible views of Red Rock Mountains.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </567597>
  <83385>
    <description>Conveniently located off the 10 freeway at the intersection of Atlantic and Hellman, Atlantic Times Square makes luxury living a practical choice. With 210 luxury condominiums set in a sprawling 200,000 square feet space full of restaurants, shops, and entertainment, you will soon realize you can have it all, and have the best of the best while you're at it! AMC theaters will be your home theater and 24 Hour Fitness will be your home gym. At the end of the day, retreat to the privacy of your home and enjoy The Residences exclusive pool, clubhouse, garden and lounge areas.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </83385>
  <470468>
    <description>GREAT OPPORTUNITY TO OWN YOUR OWN BUSINESS. CURRENTLY OPPERATING AS "TWIN KISS" ICE CREAM/FAST FOOD/ RESTAURANT. PROPERTY FRONTS LIBERTY ROAD. EXCELLANT VISIBILTY. WELL ESTABLISHED LOCATION. THIS PROPERTY HAS A DRIVE-THRU WINDOW. FREE STANDING BUILDING ON A CORNER. RIGHT NEXT DOOR TO LARGE NEW SUB-DIVISION. ALL RESTAURANT EQUIPMENT INCLUDED!!!</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </470468>
  <1002058>
    <description>Very nice unit with many upgrades. End unit provides tons of light and cross breezes that you don't get in the middle units. Close to Elgin Ohare Expressway, Stratford Square Mall and train. Close enough to Neutral decor. hardwood in family room, kitchen and eating area. Private Balcony and Private Entrance. Available towards the end of August beginning of September. All Appliances are included. All exterior maintenance is included in the rent. Don't shovel - Don't mow!Brokered And Advertised By: Re/Max Associates WestListing Agent: Laura Resnick CNC Giunti/Resnick Team Leader</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Public Transit</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1002058>
  <1085189>
    <description>Well maintained 4 plex with great rental history and cash flow. These are large 2BR apts with plenty of storage. BR 12x13; LR/Dining 16x20, Eat-In Kit 12x15. Each unit includes a storage closet in the hall. All apt appliances &amp; water softener are incl in the sale. W/D belong to service company and are not incl in sale. High efficient hot water heating system was recently installed. Opportunity to purchase additional on-site storage building is also available.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Hookup</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1085189>
  <1467061>
    <description>The City of Clinton sits along the mighty Mississippi River and is home to the Class A baseball club of the Texas Rangers. Enjoy hot meals served on site; community room for cards, parties and socializing.. Unit features: Dishwasher,Microwave Oven,Refrigerator,Stove,Air ConditioningWall,Balcony/Patio,CabinetsNew,Electric Stove,Concrete Floors,Ceiling Fans,Furnishedavailable,Garbage Disposal,Self-cleaning Oven,Vanity,View Other,Yard. Apartment Complex features: Laundry Facilities,Curbside Trash Pickup,Conference Room,Picnic Area,Patio/Balcony,Bus Line,Community Roomfor parties &amp; socializing,On-Site Management,24-Hr. Emergency Maintenance. Available Leases: 12 month,6 month. Laundry machines: On-site Laundry. Parking: Unassigned ParkingAmple. Fireplace: No</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>Garbage Disposal</amenity>
      <amenity>On-Site Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Ceiling Fan</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Public Transit</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1467061>
  <1085845>
    <description>Branchburg knoll! sought after neighborhood, convenient to everything. This 5-Br, 5.1 bath CH COL offers 3 car garage, finished walkout lower level, huge bonus room, beautiful mahogany floor throught. Many upgrades, built-in security system, irrigation system, many green features, unbelievable LOW utility bill.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1085845>
  <1154426>
    <description>Conv location for this farmhouse sits on 1/2 acre lot w/beautiful views . Spacious LR, FR &amp; DR w/built-in buffet. Office. BRs w/walk-in closets. New baths. W &amp; D hook-ups in kit. Newer windows. 8 yr. old furnace. New wtr htr &amp; conditioner. No pets/smokers</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Hookup</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1154426>
  <218706>
    <description>Riverview Landing at Valley Forge, is a distinctive vision of elegance. We are nestled in between the Schuykill River and a 40 mile tree lines biking and jogging trail. Riverview Landing has spacious one, two, and three bedroom apartments, some even have lofts. Our apartments include gourmet kitchens, nine foot ceilings, private balconies, walk-in closets, full size Whirlpool washer and dryer, Whirlpool refrigerator with ice maker, dishwasher and Whirlpool gas stove and self-cleaning oven. Relaxing in your new home right along the river could be the answer your looking for. Experience the apartments that were awarded Best In Apartment Living by the Greater Philadelphia Apartment Association in 2008 and 2009.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>Ice Maker</amenity>
      <amenity>On-Site Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </218706>
  <1465509>
    <description>Property number is 866-818-7257. Sales associates available 24 hours a day, Call Now! Experience living in a relaxed country atmosphere surrounded by mature trees and open skies. Montgomery Woods features beautifully designed one and two bedroom town homes.. Unit features: A/C Central,Balcony/Patio,Washer and Dryer Included,Closets,Dishwasher,Refrigerator,Furnished,Drapes/Blinds Included,Garbage Disposal,Walk-In Closet,Air Conditioning,Ceiling Fan,Linen Closet,Screened-in patio,Stove,Plush Carpet,Blinds,Spacious Closets,Oven,Carpet,Dining Area,Individual Heat/AC Controls,Cabinets,Kitchen,Appliances. Apartment Complex features: Jogging Trail,Pets Welcome,Courtyard,Play Ground,Outdoor Pool,24-Hour Emergency Service,Bike Paths,Patio/Balcony,On-site Maintenance,Full-Time Management Team,Walking Trails,Package Receiving Service,Sundecks,Snow Removal,Landscaping,24 Emergency Call,Trash Removal,Laundry Facilities,Private Entrances,Pool,Energy Efficient Windows. Available Leases: 12 month,6 month,Notice: 60 days. Laundry machines: Stack units included. Parking: Parking. Fireplace: No</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>Garbage Disposal</amenity>
      <amenity>On-Site Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1465509>
  <1051128>
    <description>Gypsy Hill Place is a dynamic residence for active seniors, providing 62 independent living apartments for lease. The renovated building was once the home of Robert E. Lee High School and is listed on the National Historic Register. In addition to the independent living apartments Gypsy Hill Place also provides space for the Staunton Senior Center and ShenanArts, a local community theatre non-profit.</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </1051128>
  <1367577>
    <description>At The Haven at Commons Park Luxury Apartments we offer spacious one, two and three bedroom apartment homes which feature elegant chef caliber kitchens, walk-in closets, private balconies, cozy sunrooms, wood-burning fireplaces* and washer and dryers in each unit, just to name a few. We also offer a number of community features including Free Wi-Fi Areas, Car Care Center, Resort-Style Pool plus so much more. In addition, you can take advantage of our planned community events, which include a variety of social, educational, fitness and cultural activities. Call today or visit Haven at Commons Park Luxury Apartments. First Place Winner Chattanooga Beautification Award 2009 Nominated for Best of the Best in Chattanooga 2010. Prices and Availability subject to change without notice and are based on a 6-13 month lease term with a move-in date of tomorrow. * In select units</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1367577>
  <1102797>
    <description>Three bedroom, 1 3/4 bath year round home located on Country Pond. Large Kitchen and living room. Views of Country pond from Master Bedroom and Living Room. Bedrooms are large with plenty of closet space. Mudroom and sunporch for your plants. Use the Patio adjacent to the home to play and entertain. Take the steps down to your private, sandy beach.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1102797>
  <1231290>
    <description>The Pines at Mount View in Weston, Wisconsin is a beautiful senior housing building built in a natural setting and will be finished in August 2011. Residents may choose from spacious 1 and 2 bedroom floorplans ranging in size from 748 sf to 1,223 sf. Residents have access to numerous amenities including: an elegant clubroom with fireplace and dining room, beauty/barber salon, business center, fitness center, and heated underground parking.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1231290>
  <540560>
    <description>Model 600 Townhouse. AVAILABLE MAY 15TH. No pets. No smoking. INTERIOR TO BE CLEANED and PAINTED. CARPETS TO BE SHAMPOOED. Private location backing to park-like setting. Park Spot 18-G. Eat-in kitchen. Covered patio with 2 storage closets.43-acre well-manicured community is within walking distance to Pleasant Valley Park. On-site Community Manager, playground, tennis court, clubhouse and bicycle / walking paths. Convenient to shopping and Rts 78 and 287.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </540560>
  <1132376>
    <description>We have additional shopping within a 10 minute drive from the community. We are also within minutes of the University of Oregon (Go Ducks) and the Valley River shopping center. Our innovative floor plans have 6 different designs, including: one bedroom, two bedroom, and three bedroom apartment homes; ranging in square footage from 784 to 1232. The community's unique setting has expansive views of the prairie and rolling foothills. Inside the apartment the views are no less spectacular. Kitchen pantries, spacious vaults, private balconies with additional storage, and full size washers and dryers are standard. Indulge in our immaculate fitness center, packed full of state of the art equipment. Catch up on your sports or news with the two plasma screen TVs while you burn calories. And dont feel like you have to rush, our fitness center is available 24 hours. We now have a wifi internet cafe and a Pool and Spa OPEN now!!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1132376>
  <1301036>
    <description>Tucked away on a cul-de-sac in a picturesque neighborhood sits this 5 bedroom custom home. Pool, spa, 4 car garage, 2 patios, balcony, wooded creek lot. Lake is 2 doors away. Kitchen features granite, stainless appliances, gas cooktop, subzero fridge, dbl ovens &amp; walk-in pantry.Brokered And Advertised By: Coldwell Banker ApexListing Agent: Becky Bochniak</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1301036>
  <566807>
    <description>Executive Cottage Suites offer four beautifully decorated and furnished suites located on a quiet residential street within walking distance of downtown Wenatchee. Our suites cater to business executives and medical personnel and offer a home away from home. All of our Executive Suites include the following Guest Benefits: &gt; Beautiful furnishings and d&amp;eacute;cor throughout each unit &gt; Fiber Optic wireless internet cable TV, VCR / DVD player &gt; Gorgeous living rooms and cozy dining areas &gt; Fully equipped kitchen with complimentary coffee and tea &gt; Air conditioning and electric heat &gt; Bathroom hair dryer upon request and luxurious bath towels &gt; Other amenities include digital alarm clock, iron and ironing board &gt; Maid service provided one day per week &gt; Damage Deposit NOT Required &gt; Great Patio area with furniture &amp; Grill &gt; Washer and Dryer available for all Suites Special Rates for Government and Business are available upon request when the Registration is made.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Furnished</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </566807>
  <662549>
    <description>Luxurious apartmenthomes with the ambiance of a coastal resort. Perfect for those who prefer the finest of amenities, lake front settings, water front amenities and boat docks. Above all, a secluded location with extensive landscaping to compliment the distinctive nautical architecture. Features for easy relaxation include boating, fishing and entertaining, located on the shores of beautiful Lake Pontchartrain.</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </662549>
  <977640>
    <description>Home near lake. Move-in ready by July 1st. Very nice and secluded. Ceiling fans on rooms. Two AC units installed. Laminate flooring, tiled island kitchen &amp; countertops. Utility room has washer-dryer connections. Metal storage shed or workshop at back. Fenced all around with lots of trees. NO INDOOR SMOKING and INDOOR PETS ALLOWED. Credit checks and job verification required. Agent or Tenant to verify all information.Brokered And Advertised By: Beam Real Estate, LLCListing Agent: Michelle Ramos Tan</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Hookup</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Ceiling Fan</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </977640>
  <1128601>
    <description>TAKE A MOMENT TO IMAGINE...Imagine a refreshing lifestyle that combines the charm and tranquility of a neighborhood with the convenience and service of a metropolitan area. Located in the heart of San Francisco, The Fillmore Center is surrounded by a community rich in diversity...large enough to feel like a city within the city, but intimate enough to offer everyone an inviting community spirit and a welcome retreat at the end of each day. Enjoy our complimentary SHUTTLE service to and from the Financial District every week day.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Public Transit</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1128601>
  <1341037>
    <description>I specialize in Luxury rentals and Residential Sales in Westchester, andPutnam Counties. Including, but not limited to Luxury Home &amp; Apartment Rentals in Bedford, Mt. Kisco, Pound Ridge, Katonah, North Salem, South Salem, Bedford hills, Somers, Armonk, Chappaqua, Carmel, Brewster and most of Westchester and Putnam Counties.I can assist you as your Realtor with Real Estate, Properties, Homes for Sale, Houses, Condos, Coops, New Developments, Townhomes, Townhouses, Apartments, Rentals, Fee and No Fee in the following cities in Westchester County, New York (NY), and Putnam County, New York (NY) White Plains Rye Scarsdale Harrison Mamaroneck Hartsdale Larchmont Rye Brook New Rochelle Edgemont Pelham Purchase Yonkers Bedford Mt. Kisco Ardsley Armonk Bronxville Chappaqua Dobbs Ferry Eastchester Tuckahoe Tarrytown Sleepy Hollow Irvington Brewster . Carmel . Kent . Patterson . Pawling . Katonah . Chappaqua . Bedford . Bedford Hills . Somers . Yorktown . Mahopac . North Salem . South Salem.</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </1341037>
  <1381585>
    <description>Rarely avail! Newer Baytree villa; furnished annual/seasonal or unfurn annual, ideal launch pad for discerning seasonal owners or buyers seeking to lease while bldg or finding their dream home! Stone floors, granite,stainless, fab coutyard w/pool &amp; cassita for guests/gym/office! Pet friendly, uber chic Baytree w/lush Live Oaks, knockout ocean/river pools, tennis, clubh! Lease/purch avail</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
      <amenity>Furnished</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1381585>
  <566226>
    <description>For questions or inquiries, please call us at: 866-347-8115 Oakwood Bellevue is currently running specials on two bedroom apartments starting at $1750-1850. Our two bedroom apartments are perfect for roommates with their spacious layout and split floor plans. All two bedroom apartments are corner units and have large closets and plenty of windows. Oakwood Bellevue has secured elevator lobbies and garage parking is included. Oakwood Bellevue offers amenities such as onsite fitness center,conference room, and a business center. Oakwood is a walker&amp;#39;s paradise. There are a wide variety of restaurants within two blocks. King County Regional Library within a half block. Just minutes to the U.S. Post Office. Two blocks from the Metro Transit Center. Two blocks from Downtown Business District. Minutes to freeway access - I-405, I-90, and 520. Close to a variety of Parks including Bellevue Downtown Park, Ashwood Playfield, McCormick Park, and more. The neighborhood has incredible shopping and Entertainment - Bellevue Square, Bellevue Galleria, and more.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Elevator</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
      <amenity>Public Transit</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </566226>
  <919861>
    <description>Manhattan Apartments provide a wide variety of floorplans and apartment designs including studio, one, and two bedroom apartments and two bedroom townhouse style apartments. All units feature a single bathroom design with large eat-in kitchens or living room combination. All have electric heat with individual room thermostat controls in most units. Selected units feature patios or decks, some with private access via large sliding glass doors. There are large grassy areas between all buildings and new vinyl thermo pane windows that provide plenty of light and fresh air.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </919861>
  <1383489>
    <description>Location! Midblock Totally Renovated 3Br, 2.5Bth Ranch, Lr, Den W/Fp, Cath Clgs, Hi Hats, Lg Eik, Fresh Paint, Hrdwd Flrs, Fbsmt W/Ose &amp; 2Brs, .5th, Utility, Cac, Gas Cooking, Updtd Elec, 2 Lg Closets, Igs, 2 Car Gar, Sliders In Den To Deck To Yard,Jericho Sd, Prime W. Birchwood Area. Tenant Responsible For Ground Care &amp; Utilities! Dream House!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1383489>
  <972820>
    <description>SPECTACULAR VACATION RENTAL HOME!TO RESERVE THIS HOME NIGHTLY, FOR A WEEKEND, FOR A WEEK, OR FOR A HOLIDAY &amp; TO FIND RENTAL RATES &amp; AVAILABLE DATES, PLEASE VISIT:http://www.vrbo.com/205657PROPERTY DETAILS: - This spectacular 2,400 square foot home is 1 block from the National Forest and offers 3 bedrooms, 2.5 baths, offers a large sleeping loft and sleeps 10 people comfortably. - Located 2/3 of a mile away from Bear Mountain Ski Resort, this home is located in the desirable Moonridge area of Big Bear and offers sweeping ski slope views of Bear Mountain.- This home has tons of great amenities including ski slope views, wet bar, Multiple fireplaces and dramatic soaring ceilings. This home will make your Big Bear vacation very special. - Huge double sided rock fireplace sets the tone for the house. Start a roaring fire and enjoy it from the large dining area and from the living room. - Its a very quick trip to the ski slopes to drop off or pick up the kids. After a hard day on the slopes enjoy the spa and watch the skiers and boarders as they come down for the day. - The living area is all open so the whole group can mingle while playing pool, board games, watching TV or hanging out at the bar. Every room in the house opens up to decks that look out at the ski slopes. - Bedroom #1: QUEEN BED. ATTACHED BATH. 27" TV, Opens to Deck &amp; Hot Tub. Enjoy a shower or bath in the oversized garden tub and look up through the skylight at the pine trees above. - Bedroom #2: QUEEN BED. Bath across hall. 25" TV, Opens to Deck &amp; Hot Tub. - Bedroom #3: QUEEN BED + QUEEN FUTON. 27" TV. GAS FIREPLACE IN ROOM, Bath down the hall. Opens to Deck &amp; Hot Tub - Bedroom # 4:(LOFT): QUEEN SOFA SLEEPER. 25" TV, Bath Downstairs, Private loft above living area with ski slope viewsBrokered And Advertised By: Woods Real Estate ServicesListing Agent: Christopher Hutchinson</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Furnished</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </972820>
  <1398198>
    <description>Once in a great while a gem of a property appears. This delightful home behind a white picket fence features three well-separated bedrooms with an adjacent one bedroom 600 s.f. studio. With majestic redwoods bordering, gaze out past a big garden to two enchanting ponds. Another fenced garden area with ancient greenhouse leads to the owner's 600 s.f. cottage with adjacent 600 s.f. art studio.</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </1398198>
  <22752>
    <description>Located on the Delaware Raritan Canal, the nicely landscaped Scudder Falls is set in a quiet, beautiful area of New Jersey. The on-site pool with lifeguard can make you feel like you're on vacation, yet nearby is I-95/295 with easy access to New York City and Philadelphia. Plus you are near the shopping, eating and entertainment amenities across the Delaware in Yardley as well as along Route 29 and Route 1 Corridor. Scudder Falls is also near The College of New Jersey, Rider College, the resources of downtown Trenton, and the Ewing Township school system. Inside Scudder Falls are great layouts with spacious closets. Some units boast hardwood floors, a patio or balcony, and a built-in dishwasher. Heat and hot water are included as is the on-site laundry facility and swimming pool</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>On-Site Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </22752>
  <190890>
    <description>Lakeview Apartments is a fabulous garden community conveniently and is conveniently located to express bus service to NYC. Cats are welcome, additional fees and restrictions apply. Beautiful landscaping and your own private entrance welcomes you home to Lakeview Apartments. Our newly renovated homes feature gas cooking, energy star appliances, dishwasher, microwave and ceramic tile baths. Each spacious floor plan offers great closet space, thermal-pane windows with vertical blinds included, and air conditioning. Verizon FiOS is available. Amazing amenities include a new fitness center, playground, picnic area, and on-site parking. Garages are available for rent. Lakeview Apartments is located in the Leonia School District, not far from Fort Lee, and is convenient to NJ Transit trains and buses, the George Washington Bridge, and local parks, shopping and dining. Come tour your new home at Lakeview Apartments. Call today!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>Cats Allowed</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
      <amenity>Public Transit</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </190890>
  <264074>
    <description>Refurbished Second Floor Condo with All New Appliances and Paint. Centrally located in the Center of Dennisport at Harborside Condominium Complex close to Shopping and Restaruants. Has 2 Good size Bedrooms with Paddle Fans to Keep you Cool in the Summer and an Air Conditioner in the Living Room. Coin Operated Laundry in the Basement and Private Storage. Assigned Parking Space. Most Utilities Included. A Must See Unit.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>On-Site Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </264074>
  <1209029>
    <description>Our property is conveniently located near I-695, I-97, and Ritchie Highway. Units include the following great amenities spacious closest, cable ready, wall to wall carpeting. Call to schedule your personal tour today! Give us a call before you miss out on this great special! Pet Policy: Max. Number of Pets 2, Pet Rent: $25 Per Month Restricted Breeds: Pit Bull, Doberman, &amp; Rotweiler</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Dogs Allowed</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1209029>
  <1420740>
    <description>One and two bedroom garden apartment and three bedroom lofts. All of the apartments have washer/dryer hook-ups and carport included. Fireplace optional.. Unit features: Garbage Disposal,Balcony/Patio,Carpet,Central Air,Dishwasher,Blinds,Electric Stove,FireplaceIn Select Units,Refrigerator,Loftin Townhouse Floorplan,Walk-In Closet,Ceiling Fanselect units,Linen Closetselect units,Vaulted Ceilingselect units. Apartment Complex features: Parking-Coveredassigned,Basketball Court,Fitness Center,Outdoor Pool,Racquetball Court,Laundry Facilities,Tennis Court,Ice Maker,Microwave,Picnic Areapoolside. Available Leases: 12lease terms are flexible,3,6. Laundry machines: Coin Operated - In Central Building,Hook-ups Provided. Parking: CarportOne Included w/Each Unit,Off-street Parking. Fireplace: Yes</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>Garbage Disposal</amenity>
      <amenity>On-Site Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>In-Unit Hookup</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Ceiling Fan</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1420740>
  <1167912>
    <description>2nd floor single room OFFICE SPACE - highway. Rt 23 &amp; 287 within sight. Rts 46,80,10,208 &amp; 17 a short drive but convenient for your clients or employees - FACES RT 23. *Office size is approx. 14'6 x 18' plus use of the common area approx. 9' x 24'. Plus use of the bathroom. Clean, freshly painted - great space - Your own private office with shared common area - reception - rest room -// If your home is not the place for you to conduct business, why not have YOUR OWN BUSINESS SPACE- -- or if Economic times are suggeting that you DOWNSIZE your office space --- Lease an office in this convenient location-- Route 23 location - utilities included.</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </1167912>
  <1002989>
    <description>Spacious, doublewide with metal roof &amp; vinyl siding on 2 landscaped by nature, acres. Completely fenced with chain link fencing with lockable entry gates. Guest cabin (1BD/1BTH) is not much but would make a great work out room or man cave. Screened cook room was designed for frying fish &amp; bar-b-ques. Triple bay workshop with lockable tool room is under the shade trees out back. Carport and two additions add to the main home which is a 1995, 3 BD/2BTH, with over 2000 sq. ft. home. Former owner reports that the front addition was built on and designed to be the smoking porch (it is heated &amp; cooled) with many windows to allow for optimum air flow. Back additions have concrete slabs &amp; indoor/outdoor carpet &amp; were originally the craft/sewing room and the train collection rooms. The rooms on the back are now used for over flow storage, they have many windows to see the entire property on the North grounds including the detached workshop/cook room &amp; patio swing. Multiple faucets are located all around the 2 acres for busy gardeners.Brokered And Advertised By: All Realty ServicesListing Agent: Lynette C. Sirmon</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1002989>
  <498588>
    <description>Stylish One Bedroom/One Bath in a oceanfront building on the Gold Coast. Unit is fully furnished with a full kitchen and washer/dryer. One parking stall included. Rent is $3,900/per month. This unit is also avaialable for long-term leases - contact Jeanne directly for details. Please visit www.goldcoasthawaii.com for additional information and booking link.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Furnished</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </498588>
  <495630>
    <description>Our property is conveniently located near public parks, schools, dining and the famous Camarillo Outlets. Property grounds feature resort like landscaping, BBQ grills and outdoor fireplaces. Unit amenities include elegant kitchens with cherry wood cabinets, granite countertops, Gas Ranges, Two-tone paint, Washer and Dryer in every unit, and private entrances.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </495630>
  <439340>
    <description>Sublet.com Listing ID 550956. An Efficiency with Maine Ambiance. Second floor private entrance with sun deck. Queen bed plus daybed lounge in sitting area. Fully equipped kitchen. Skylit bath with glass shower. Linens provided. Just bring your clothes personal items. Cable TV, DVD and CD player. Pet may be OK. Walk to harbor, shops all.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Furnished</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </439340>
  <933827>
    <description>17th Place is under New Management and striving daily to make your next move your last move. We pride ourselves in meeting the needs of all our Residents. Our office staff is friendly and the Maintenance team is prompt in making repairs. Our community has government assisted housing (sec.8). With gas prices these days, we could all use a little assistance with paying our rent ( income and other restrictions do apply) Our community is conveniently located within minutes of parks, schools and shopping. We are looking forward to welcoming you home, See you soon.</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </933827>
  <1131626>
    <description>Studio, 1 bedroom, 1 bedroom plus den and 2 bedroom apartments for rent in Saint Paul, MN at The Cosmopolitan located in the Lowertown area of downtown. The 1920s architecture features a beautifully decorated and contemporary lobby and a unique vaulted curved ceiling with a spectacular skyscape mural. Apartments offer the ultimate luxury-commanding views of Mears Park, the Mississippi River and downtown St. Paul. You have your choice of a wide variety of spacious apartments, many with innovative platform designs, large dens and fashionable lofts. Ceiling heights soar, and oversized windows drench each room in sunlight. There is a European-style, fully equipped gourmet kitchen with microwave oven, and a convenient pass-through counter, 16 foot ceilings, individually controlled heating and air conditioning, in-home washer and dryer, walk-in closets and a camera-identification system that protects the privacy you deserve.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1131626>
  <517270>
    <description>*3 bedrooms / 2 baths *1325 Square feet *Wood flooring and ceramic tile in kitchen and baths *Open floor plan *2 Car garage *Fenced in backyard *Large windows *Quiet neighborhood *Great neighbors *Includes refrigerator, washer &amp; dryer, dishwasher, microwave *Short commute to Lafayette or New Iberia *Lafayette Airport ? 5 minutes *Interstate 10 ? 10 minutes *Nearby ? Wal-mart, Albertsons, movie theatre, shopping, restaurants ~ 12 Month Lease ~ $1300 a month ~ $1300 Deposit ~ Pets considered ~ Available NOW ~Non-smokers only</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </517270>
  <1418310>
    <description>Ask about our flexible leasing terms and pricing to meet your specific needs.. Unit features: Balcony/Patio,Spacious Floorplans,Walk-in Closets,Washer and Dryer Included,Storage,Carpet,Crown Molding,Air Conditioning,Dishwasher. Apartment Complex features: Landscaping,Outdoor Pool,Sundecks,Dog Park,Close to Beach,Close to Schools,Close to Shopping,Close to Restaurants. Available Leases:. Laundry machines:. Parking:. Fireplace: No</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Dogs Allowed</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1418310>
  <1167952>
    <description>Large single family home in the country with lots of natural sunlight. Entrance through beautiful refreshing sunroom with both heat and central air conditioning. All newer lighting, heating &amp; air conditioning, appliances, flooring, electric and plumbing. Easy to maintain flooring for your welcome pets (case-by-case basis). Garage available under separate lease.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1167952>
  <519876>
    <description>Cabin, AT WATERS EDGE, with sleeping alcove and additional queen sleeper, with 1 bath, full laundry, full kitchen, fireplace, TV &amp; living area with covered stone porch, great for BBQ, dining out, playing your guitar. Sleeps 5 with roll out. Cabin is on acreage with rushing trout water, landscaped pond and waterfall all in front yard. Open the window and listen to the music of the trout stream. On property with another home that sleeps up to 7 and another across and down which sleeps 5. All can be rented as one package. These homes never rented to two seperate families. We want you to have exclusive rights to the property. Come enjoy the Mountain fresh air. Send Email herewith and or call: 770 359 8834 and or 770 666 3298.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </519876>
  <1031227>
    <description>See more details at http://cobblestone.appfolio.com/listings/012d8747-f61a-41d5-9e46-bd7d313d7dfa Recently updated! New slab granite in kitchen, new hardwood floors, new SS range, and some new paint. Spacious lot with East facing backyard next to protected open space. Relax on the private flagstone courtyard and true wrap-around porch for easy outdoor living and views. Grand fireplace in airy great room. Elegant formal dining. Main level master and adjoining sun room.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1031227>
  <1569534>
    <description>Galleria at Towngate is a private, gated community that offers one of the largest floor plans in Moreno Valley. We feature outstanding amenities that include a sparkling pool and spa, barbecue and picnic areas, state-of-the-art business center and a fully-equipped fitness center. We're conveniently located near all sorts of shopping that include a regional shopping mall, grocery stores, movie theaters and well-known restaurants. You'll also enjoy nearby walking, hiking and biking trails at Box Springs Mountain Park and Sycamore Canyon Wilderness Park.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1569534>
  <716638>
    <description>Enjoy a master planned 55+ adult community in the heart of King City. We offer a fantastic location that is nestled adjacent to a beautiful golf course. We are within walking distance to the King City Community Center and Plaza with great shopping, restaurants, and much more. Join our residents who are interested in continuing the adventure of life.</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </716638>
  <1167737>
    <description>This 2 story home features 3 bedrooms, 2.5 bathrooms and over 1600 square feet. It has a large open living room with fireplace, formal dining room and breakfast nook next to the kitchen. The house is located in a newer subdivision with a huge pool, tennis courts and clubhouse. Located just off of Shiloh Church Rd near Hwy 73. Convenient to Concord and Huntersville. All appliances included.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1167737>
  <561567>
    <description>Newer upscale home offers 4 bedrooms 3 bathroom. Granite kitchen counters with newer appliances. Wood floors throughout with carpet in each bedroom. Gas fireplace. Slider off dining to patio and backyard. Close to school, city center, resturants and short walk to beach. $1600 per month first and last months rent requiered along with $500 cleaning deposit a portion can be made refundable.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </561567>
  <966523>
    <description>140 Highland Circle is available for rent at $1200 per month. Split level home on large .85 acre lot. Features over 1362 SQ Ft of finished space, fam room w/ coal stove &amp; fire place, eat in kitchen / solid surface counters, hardwood floors, updated roof &amp; gutters, carport w/ shed, patio /pavers, and privacy to the rear.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </966523>
  <294201>
    <description>Beautiful townhouse in downtown Pilot Mountain with 3 bedrooms and 3.5 bathrooms! Enjoy the main level master bedroom and laundry. Garage. End unit. Call today! Brokered And Advertised By: Realty World Brantley &amp; Associates Listing Agent: Bryant Brantley</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </294201>
  <464568>
    <description>Well kept, Owner occupied first floor unit. Has newer sheetrock and electric, hardwood flooring, a cozy wood burning stove, plus a nice kitchen. Enjoy your cool cozy spring and summertime evenings on a nice wooden deck and private back yard. Conveniently located right off of Route 168, area bridges leading to Philadelphia and close to area shopping centers. Not to mentioned it is also located in the sought after Haddon Township School District. Owner relocating and is looking for the right tenant.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </464568>
  <1018172>
    <description>Newly remodeled 3 Bedroom unit in Newton District. Recently remodeled apartment features new paint, carpet, windows, kitchen, appliances, and bathrooms. Large unit with lots of natural light, and a Fully Fenced back yard provide privacy. Very Affordable unit that has city services. Call us today!!</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </1018172>
  <1380956>
    <description>1200 sq. ft., 2nd floor, open floor plan w/vaulted ceilings, tiled living area, eat-in kitchen, W/D, MBR suite w/large walk-in shower, screen balcony w/golf course views, extra storage, community pool, golfing, close to shopping.Save $130 = FREE Cable TV/ water!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1380956>
  <1049316>
    <description>Large 3BD, 2BA in quiet Elon neighborhood. Close to Elon University and downtown Elon. Amenities include:- Offstreet Parking- Washer and Dryer- Dishwasher- Central Air and Heat- 2 full BA- Microwave- Trash Disposer- large BDs, kitchen, and living area- large deck- Like new Refrigerator and Range - OvenAct quickly. This rental would not last for a long time.Call us today at (336) 617-4596.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1049316>
  <1305203>
    <description>1/1 695 ++ Square Feet....Nice Apartment Homes!!..Super Location...Within minutes to DFW Airport!...Amenities +++...Garages Available, Limited Access Gates &amp; Private Alarms, Business Center, Theater Room &amp; State of the Art Fitness Center, Golf Putting Green, Walking Trails... Nice Clubhouse...Olympic-Style Pool w/Hot Tub... Sand Volleyball, Basketball,Playground...Social Activities..... Berber Carpet/Hardwood Flooring...Gourmet Style Kitchens ...Appliances including Microwave, Granite Counter-tops, Crown Molding, Built-in Bookshelves, Ceiling Fans...and Of Course, Wonderful Garden Tubs!! Local/Caring/Stable Management!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Ceiling Fan</amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1305203>
  <892662>
    <description>Our spacious one and two bedroom floorplans offer exclusive features such as a washer and dryer in every home, central heat and air condition unit, breakfast bar, ceiling fan, and private patios in select floorplans. Enjoy our three refreshing pools and spa, children tot lot, visit our fitness center, or get some work done in our business center. Emerald Ridge is conveniently located near the 60, 605 and 57 freeways as well as many restaurants, shopping and entertainment opportunities. We are also conveniently near Rio Hondo College and Mt San Antonio College. Visit Emerald Ridge today and enjoy quality living in a harmonious environment. You will be happy you found us! NEW pricing!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Ceiling Fan</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </892662>
  <433010>
    <description>Sublet.com Listing ID 1605471. Quiet, comfortably furnished cottage on the water near Sag Harbor village. Walk to town beach. Flexible days or monthly JanuaryApril only. Utilities included. Onsite parking. One nonsmoking person only. References security deposit required.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Furnished</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </433010>
  <570494>
    <description>Start living a legacy at Legacy at Manchester Village, offering you a place to play and a place to live. Now that you are looking to make your next move... step out of the ordinary and into something special. The stylish apartment home interiors offer you space for entertaining, space for relaxing and even space to study. Our community has space to spare with detached garages and additional storage space accomodations. Legacy at Manchester Village is located across from the beautiful Manchester Meadows park and directly behind the Manchester Village Center. The Manchester Village center offers you the convenience of dozens of restaurants, 40,000 square feet of shopping and a stadium seating multi-plex theatre. As you can see this community has everything you need right at your fingertips. So call today and start living a legacy.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </570494>
  <1213638>
    <description>Williamsburg Townhomes are the only apartments within the prestigious planned community of Greenwood Village in Sagamore Hills. Residents choose Williamsburg because of the ideal location adjacent to the Cuyahoga Valley National Park and the direct trail access to the Towpath Trail. Williamsburg is located twenty miles from downtown Cleveland and downtown Akron, and is seven miles from the rapidly growing business center of Independence. This community offers townhome apartments with attached garages, and an extensive amenities package including two outdoor pools, one indoor pool, poolside WiFi, fitness center, tennis courts, and more.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1213638>
  <1002331>
    <description>FOR SALE or LEASE or LEASE/PURCHASE! Versatile 10-office building with 10 entrances, completely remodeled in 2006. Walk-in level: lobby/reception, 4 private offices, double staff work area, conference room w/custom cabinetry, break room, 3 restrooms, 4 entrances. Upper level: 5 offices, 3 restrooms, 6 entrances. Private brick courtyard. 27 parking spaces. Easy in/out via 2 curb cuts on 150' Osage Beach Pkwy. frontage. Lighted sign/marquee. 1,320 sq. ft. garage/workshop w/overhead door &amp; adjoining 576 sq. ft. utility building. Income from 10,000 sq. ft. fenced gravel area w/garage leased to Charter Communications. Just east of Grand Glaize Bridge, and just west of new Passover Road stoplight.Brokered And Advertised By: McNally PropertiesListing Agent: Pat McNally</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </1002331>
  <7179>
    <description>Charlotte Court Apartments is a charming Antigo apartment community located just steps away from the convenience of shopping, dining, and entertainment. If you desire a great location and beautifully designed apartments with expansive floor plans, Charlotte Court Apartments is the community for you. Each luxury apartment includes heat and comes with a garage, full size washer/dryer, and a private veranda. Our professional and friendly staff is here to assist you and welcome you home to Charlotte Court Apartments.</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Garage</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </7179>
  <345414>
    <description>See more details at http://robertmasseyco.appfolio.com/listings/5e7ac766-1608-4852-a2f6-0c13d9a96140 Beautiful 3 bedroom 2 bath single family home with a range, dishwasher, screened in porch off livingroom, deck, finished basement, huge fended in yard, and SO MUCH MORE!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </345414>
  <463931>
    <description>Discover an emerging growth area as other retail business owners have in the borough of Parkesburg! This is NEW CONSTRUCTION with a potential clientele of 72 SAge-Qualified Living Apartments on 2nd, 3rd and 4th Floors. There is a proposed 290 Unit Townhome Community 2.4 mi North, a New Retail Center Proposed 2.3 mi North and ~Parkesburg Knoll~ New Construction - Over 80 New Homes 0.9 mi (just blocks away. Great for retail sales or service-related business. Four Retail Suites available - all storefront - great visibility. Negotiable lease terms and fit out options.</description>
    <amenities type="array"/>
  </463931>
  <523671>
    <description>Timeshare unit in Park City, Utah owned by listing agent. Available quarterly for 2 one week periods. Price per week varies with the season &amp; dates. Fully furnished 2 bedroom, 2 bath condo with full kitchen at the bottom of historic Main Street just 1 block of the Town Lift to Park City Ski Resort. Indoor sauna &amp; hot tub + outdoor hot tub. Free bus transportation around Park City. 3 major ski areas within minutes. Walk to restaurants &amp; shopping!!</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Public Transit</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </523671>
  <416673>
    <description>Rates start at $699.00. Free application fee if you apply within 24 hours of 1st viewing. Hardwood floors available. Quick occupancy available.. Unit features: Outside Entrance,Carpet,Central Air,Dishwasher,Electric Stove,Refrigerator,Garbage Disposal,Furnished Corporate Unit,Hardwood Floors,Private Entrance,Ceiling Fan,Basement,Fully Equipped Kitchens,Washer and Dryer Included,Alarm System,Central Heat-A/C,Spacious Closets,Spacious Floorplans,Breakfast Bar,Balcony/Patio,Blinds,Self-cleaning Oven,Bay Window,A/C Central,Heat -Central,Stove,Closets,Vertical Blinds,Walk-In Closet. Apartment Complex features: Alarms-Intrusion,Bus Line,Pets Welcome,Club Housew/ Fireplace,Sauna,Computer Center,Package Receiving Service,Outdoor Pool,Fitness Center,Social Activities,On-site Maintenance,24-Hr. Emergency Maintenance,Internet Access-DSL. Available Leases: Notice: 60 days,Month-to-month,12 month,6 month,9 month,short term available for additional fee,12months. Laundry machines: Full size units included,W/D Included. Parking: Off-street Parking,Unassigned Parking. Fireplace: No</description>
    <amenities type="array">
      <amenity>Dishwasher</amenity>
      <amenity>Garbage Disposal</amenity>
      <amenity>In-Unit Laundry</amenity>
      <amenity>Pet Friendly</amenity>
      <amenity>Cats Allowed</amenity>
      <amenity>Dogs Allowed</amenity>
      <amenity>Air conditioning</amenity>
      <amenity>Ceiling Fan</amenity>
      <amenity>Heat </amenity>
      <amenity>Balcony  deck  or patio</amenity>
      <amenity>Wood floors</amenity>
      <amenity>Parking</amenity>
      <amenity>Public Transit</amenity>
      <amenity>Gym/Fitness</amenity>
      <amenity>Pool</amenity>
    </amenities>
  </416673>
</hash>
